cultofmac.com 2019-06-24

# Cult of Mac's privacy policy | Cult of Mac

[ ](https://www.cultofmac.com/privacy-policy/) Here's everything you need to know about _Cult of Mac'_ s privacy policy.   
_Photo: Ste Smith/Cult of Mac_

### Your privacy is important to us

At [_Cult of Mac_](http://www.cultofmac.com/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by our website, located at https://www.cultofmac.com,  and how it is used.

**General**  
In general, _Cult of Mac_ collects some non-identifiable information about visitors to our site that we sometimes share with third parties to perform services on our behalf, and we obtain consent for such sharing where legally required. The third-party providers used by us will only collect, use and disclose your information to the extent necessary to allow them to perform the services they provide to us.

**Log files**  
Like many other websites, _Cult of Mac_ makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, internet service provider (ISP), date/timestamp, referring/exit pages and number of clicks. This data enables us to administer the site, analyze trends, track users’ movements around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such data is not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and web beacons**  
_Cult of Mac_ uses cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**Advertising cookies and web beacons**  
Google, our primary third-party advertising vendor, uses [DoubleClick cookies](https://support.google.com/adsense/answer/2839090?hl=en) to serve ads on the _Cult of Mac_ website. Google’s use of cookies enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to CultofMac.com and other sites. Users may control the ads Google serves by visiting [Google’s ad settings page](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/)

Some of our other advertising partners, including Digital Trends, may use cookies and web beacons on our site. (We also utilize affiliate links, which you can read about on the [_Cult of Mac_ reviews policy page](http://www.cultofmac.com/cult-of-mac-reviews-policy/), and these affiliate vendors may use cookies as well.)

These third-party ad servers automatically receive your IP address from your web browser when you visit our site. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript and web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content you see.

These technologies collect information that is not personally identifiable (e.g., the pages you visit, which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our website.

These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third-party web beacon to collect this information.

If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

_Cult of Mac_ has no access to or control over cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices, as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices.

_Cult of Mac’_ s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or websites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### For more information

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@cultofmac.com.
